Such
Such big frogs
Per the contract requirements
Each weighs over 200 grams
The fat content is no less than
95%
Walter
You can inspect them now
Mr. Lewes
These frogs are so huge
Did you also feed them
With that hormone feed
Absolutely not
If you're worried
Feel free to test them
If even one frog has issues
I'll compensate on the spot
With the 30 million penalty
Mr. Walter
The test results are out
These frogs have no hormone residue
All metrics pass
Fat content is 97%
Excellent quality
They are the best
forest frogs our company has ever received
Mr. Lewes
Your frog-raising skills
Really impress me
I'll have the finance
Transfer the 10 million payment
To your account immediately
Also
I want to sign the next contract with you
With no penalty clause
I trust you
Pleasure doing business